Guide to the Yale Law School Photographs of Events, Activities, and Individuals
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale Law School photographs of events, activities, and individuals
1860-1970
RU 749
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
1.75
The materials consist of images documenting faculty, students, alumni, and the Justianian Society of the Yale Law School.
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 26 (YRG 26), Records of the Yale Law School.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of images documenting faculty, students, alumni, and the Justianian Society of the Yale Law School.
Photographs; Yale Law School; Yale University -- Alumni and alumnae; Yale University -- Faculty; Yale University -- Students
- Photographs, Circa 1874-1970
  - Photographs (Box 1)
  - OVERSIZE
    - Alumni
      - Classes of 1890, 1891, 1892 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Classes of 1893, 1897 (50th reunion), 1901, 1947 June (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Class of 1915 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - General faculty pictures, Circa 1900, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Faculty, Circa 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Justinian Society, 1867 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Law Journal Board
      - 1904-1906 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - 1906-1908 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - 1923-1927, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - FOLIO
    - Alumni, 1874-1909 (Box DR13F42)
    - Alumni, 1914-1942 (Box DR14F43)
    - Law Journal Board, 1941-1942 (Box DR14F43)
    - Law School crest (Box DR15F47)
- Portraits of instructors and alumni affiliated with the Yale Law School, Circa 1860-1921; Accession 2001-A-046
  - Photographs, etchings, and lithographic prints of individuals
    - Arellons, Cayetans S., YLS 1904. (Donated to the Yale Law School by Salvadore Zaragoza) (Box 1)
    - Brenner, David, YLS 1856 (Box 1)
    - Brown, Henry B., YLS 1856 (Box 1)
    - Choute, Rufus, YLS 1895 (Box 1)
    - Davis, David, YLS 1834 (Box 1)
    - Dwight, Theodore W., YLS 1841 (1904) (Box 1)
    - Evans, Mr. M, Men of Work (signed by Evans, 1884) (Box 1)
    - Evarts, William M., YLS 1837 (Box 1)
    - Shiras, George, Jr., YLS 1853 (Box 1)
  - Photograph of the Yale University Band taken during the Yale-Princeton football game at the Yale Bowl, 1921 November 12 (Box 1)